In space there is no daylight.
Dracula 3000 is a horror, science fiction film directed by Darrell James Roodt.
In the year 3000, the deep space salvage ship Mother III locates the
vanished starship Demeter in the Carpathian System.
Captain Abraham Van Helsing and his crew composed of the blonde assistant Aurora Ash; the crippled navigator Arthur "The Professor" Holmwood, who believes
that he is a genius; the strong and dumb Humvee; the intern Mina Murry; and the drug addicted 187, decide to claim the possession of Demeter.
While exploring the spacecraft, they see a tape of fifty years ago of Captain Varna telling that he was locked in
his cabin since his crew was acting weird after getting a cargo of coffins in Transylvania station.
When 187 decides to search in the coffins for some possible hidden dope,
he cuts his hand and his blood awakes Count Orlock, a.k.a.
Count Dracula.
When Aurora discloses who Dracula is, the survivors try
to find a way to destroy the vampire.
Capt. Abraham Van Helsing, played by Casper Van Dien.
Aurora Ash, played by Erika Eleniak.
Mina Murry, played by Alexandra Kamp.
187, played by Coolio.
Arthur "The Professor" Holmwood, played by Grant Swanby.
Orlock, played by Langley Kirkwood.
Dracula 3000 (stylized as DRACULA.3000, and also known as Dracula 3000: Infinite Darkness) is a
2004 made-for-television science fiction horror film directed by Darrell Roodt.
An international co-production of Germany and South Africa, it is an adaptation of
Bram Stoker's novel Dracula in the futuristic setting of outer space.
Despite its title, the film is not connected to the Dracula 2000 series.
The film explores themes of space marine, vampire,
matter of life and death, dracula.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.